If you have a job and you pay your PF every month,
this is news for you.
Understand in a simple language
The interest on PF is exactly like the interest on bank.
That is, as much money as you have in your PF account.
EPFO pays a certain amount of extra money on that money every
year called interest.
This time, EPFO decided to pay 8.25% interest on PFs.
Now the question is how and when will we get this money?
EPFO has started the interest deposit process.
But it takes a little while to update millions of accounts at
once.
So if you don 't have this interest show in your account
yet
So it's not a matter of being shocked.
In the coming days, this money will be added to your PF
account.
And you get the interest of the whole year together.
You don't have to do anything to see if interest has come.
You can check the interest updated by going to the EPFO's passport
book.
If that is the case, then understand that your money has arrived.
Understood in straightforward language
As much money as you deposit in the PF
EPFO pays him some extra money every year.
And this time, this money will be deposited in your account at
a rate of 8.25%.